With Life Time Warranty.  I have never
ordered jewelry online before.
Before I tell you what I
ordered from Pulmona.
So hello guys, I recently ordered some
jewellery from Pulmonas.  So let's try that.
I ordered these earrings
and this is a bangle.  I had
already unboxed it because I was very
excited about what all would
come inside.  It feels so good, friend.
Nice.  I ordered it from the monsoon sale.
Three were coming for Rs 3000.  3000 were for
1000.  This gift came on that one.
You can see it has a double chain.  Nice.  We had
ordered sets of three.  Sister is
looking for the jewellery that she wore.  So
I have the boxes and I
will wear mine now.  Why is it so hot?